testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
Hi
Hi. Hi.
Hi.
Flover
The first week
is over.
Today
I'm back to short hair.
Short hair
But since I had long hair
recently
now I kind of want to do long hair again you know?
Go in
go in
go in go in
It's not going in.
My hair
was so pretty today right guys?
Huh? Vitamin B 57?
Already?
Oh why?
Why? Why? Why?
Why? Did something
happen
to us?
What
what what
went
well?
Why?
Why is it?
Suddenly
really
I'm getting dizzy.
Really
thank you.
Flover
Today
since the first week is over I just
my makeup
today
is kind of ruined.
The members might be a bit tired
but
I
slept
a lot today.
I
might take off
this necklace soon.
I wanted to do red
didn't I?
I look a bit spacey right now because I took out my contacts.
I shouldn't have taken them out.
But today
um
did you see the performance? Inkigayo.
I have something I want to brag about.
At Inkigayo today
how should I say it?
They gave me the ending fairy.
Thankfully
they gave me
the ending like this
uh
what was I saying oh
they gave me the ending
at Inkigayo
I thought they gave it to me
because I looked pretty today
and
wore blue.
But today I
really waited a long time
to wear this outfit
so fast.
I waited a long time.
I only wanted to wear this outfit because I like blue
and it was so hard only wearing pink all this time. I was so upset.
Since I kept
not being able to wear blue.
But
I was so happy
to finally
wear blue.
Ah my face today suddenly
suddenly
looks a bit weird
since I let my hair down.
Um.
I look a bit exhausted right? I have to look exhausted because I did this makeup
at 3 AM.
Was it 3 AM or 4 AM?
Dawn
so I've been keeping this
makeup on
for almost 20 hours now
so you
have to take into account
that I might look
a little exhausted.
Anyway
what I wanted to say is about Inkigayo
so
I
really paid attention
today
and
was looking forward to today's hair makeup and outfit
so I
worked hard
was looking forward to today's hair makeup and outfit
talking with the hair stylists
worked hard
was looking forward to today's hair makeup and outfit
talking with the hair stylists
from a few days ago
and
because of that
I thought I looked pretty today
and
figured that's why they gave me the ending
but it turns out
that wasn't it.
That wasn't it.
My
friend
my friend
named Park Jiwoo
you know.
I want to give her a shoutout
she's
an actress
our Jiwoo
was an MC
for Inkigayo in the past.
And recently
she must have met
with the director and writer. And there
she told them my friend
is making a comeback soon
so please look after her well
that's what Jiwoo told them.
Park Jiwoo are you watching?
I actually contacted her just earlier
to say thanks
so
they took really good care of me.
Inkigayo totally.
So they even filmed
my facecam twice
I was so thankful
I felt so good.
So
thanks.
I really benefited from having a good friend.
Right? Having a good friend
my only
friend and now
since I have a good friend
anyway Inkigayo
today's outfit kind of reminded me of the Stay This Way era too
and everyone
liked it so much so I felt really great.
And blue
it was a blue outfit so I loved it.
Our concept today
was kind of Ariel.
So
I even put blue highlighter on the front here like this
and stuff.
And
what was I going to say?
Anyway
did you guys
have a favorite
outfit?
The white outfit we wore
more people liked it
than I thought.
I didn't know you guys would like it that much.
Fluffy puppy
right.
Music Bank
I thought the M Countdown outfit was really pretty too
yesterday at Music Core
they really
paid a lot of attention to us
Ah actually
we made so many mistakes
during the camera rehearsal. With the members
we
were stumbling
and stuttering
and missing all the timings
like
fourth place who
we had to say it like this but
we were saying third place when third place came out and stuff. Just as an example
so
the members really
focused hard
during the live broadcast
and said let's definitely not mess up. Let's not mess up.
Let's absolutely not mess up but
then
Hayoung made a cute mistake
so that
was cute. I looked at Hayoung and
asked her to make a mistake
beforehand.
I said it'd be really cute if you made a mistake Unnie.
Like
do it on purpose
and pretend it's a mistake.
Do it.
Just mess up a bit.
But
I didn't know she would actually mess up like that.
But it's cute.
Anyway our original content is so
fun isn't it?
Ah somehow
I want to take off this necklace and put on another one.
Hmm
not this one
that purple.
Sky blue.
It's sky blue.
Ta-da.
How is it?
I brought a blue one. A blue one
ta-da.
Anyway
we went with blue
for today.
What
was I going to say?
What was I talking about before I leave?
Anyway we were talking about our outfits
but isn't our original content
so fun? Yesterday
I really
think the things uploaded yesterday are so funny.
Really
yesterday
Mimiminu's
video
was so funny too
and that
our Idol Human Theater
isn't Idol Human Theater so funny too guys?
Idol Human Theater was so funny
the members
really really
laughed so much
we could barely film it. But
doesn't Jiwon Unnie sing live so well? I was shocked listening to that
while performing.
Wow
BDNS
BDNS is
fun too. I looked at the comments
for the BDNS
video but there was nothing about me.
I'm upset.
People only said I look intimidating
and
I'm so upset. Tell me I'm pretty too.
I was at
Lotteria too
but no one talked about me
I really like Lotteria though
so I was hurt.
Yeah.
You're writing a comment now?
Forget it.
I don't need it.
It's already too late.
Anyway
since so many people
liked it
when I wore the mint outfit I feel really good.
Actually today
the staff members and everyone
complimented me saying mint suits me well
but the members were a bit annoyed
the older members said
it's a bit annoying that I wore mint
and it looks like I'm trying to follow the trend
so I said that's right I'm trying to follow the trend
let me be the mint devil.
Mint devil.
Should I try wearing mint clothes?
Should I go put on some mint clothes?
Now
remember.
This is
purple.
I'll try wearing mint.
Wait a sec.
How is it?
This kind of vibe.
With this kind of
vibe
how is it?
Hold on.
Ta-da.
This is
down to here
Miss
Mint
a total
mint girl
now I've transformed.
Ta-da.
But I don't like mint chocolate.
Guys
mint chocolate is
but mint itself is fine.
Looking at it
it suddenly got refreshing right.
It feels
very much like
summer.
Look here.
Things like this are all mint too.
Ta-da. Ta-da.
Actually ah this is my first time opening it.
Behind the scenes of this music show.
Wow this time music shows
among all the
uh music shows so far
were the most
hectic I think.
It feels like
it went by really quickly?
At home too
like
every single day
I would just sleep
and like this
the day would
pass by
so somehow
without thinking about whether today is yesterday
or yesterday is today
just passing time
like this but
that's why
it was actually better.
Being so busy like this
Flovers must have been really tired too
well.
Ta-da.
Cute right?
These are probably gifts I received from fans. This one probably too
oh no.
Yesterday
MC
is Gag Concert on?
Then I should turn this off.
What's this? I'll do this again later guys.
Go watch Gag Concert. Bye.